<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AristoCat</string>

    <string name="maximus_name">MAXIMUS</string>
    <string name="maximus_nick">THE ACCLAIMED HERO</string>
    <string name="maximus_moto">THERE IS NO SUCH THING AS PAIN, ONLY VICTORY.</string>
    <string name="maximus_abstract">He puts the \'A\' in Aristeia! The epitome and defender of the grand values that define this sport, a natural-born leader, protector of his companions, and scourge of his opponents, Maximus\' resplendent smile and shield-bearing silhouette fan the flames of passion in the hearts of sports fans across the Human Sphere.\n</string>
    <string name="maximus_description">Maximus is the square-jawed hero every kid in the Human Sphere wants to grow up to become. Maximus is the \‘A\’ in Aristeia!\n
        Most Aristeia! fighters build a persona around their unique abilities and equipment, a bigger-than-life canvas on which to project a compelling story. By dint of editing and various audio-visual technologies, they forge their legend as superheroes or fearsome heels in the eyes of billions.\n
        Maximus is no exception to this, but he also serves a political function. He lives out a message PanOceania is constantly broadcasting to Humankind at large, playing the role that the hyperpower claims to play for the Human Sphere. He\’s the shield of Justice that makes order possible, the armor that safeguards the standard of living every society is entitled to. Maximus is the perfect stand-in and spokesman for his nation: Courteous and unfailingly wholesome, yet still a titanic, unassailable bulwark.\n
        In the HexaDome, as in his many feature mayafilms, Maximus plays the lead. He offsets the limitations of his bulk with masterful positioning, and can serve his tactical roles—zone defense, man-to-man lockdown, teammate coverage—robustly despite his lack of serious firepower.\n
        Maximus is the epitome of fair play and teamwork. He\’s been at the peak of the competition for a whooping eight years and is showing no signs of slowing down.\n
        \“Say your prayers and eat your vitamins!\”</string>

    <string name="parvati_name">PARVATI</string>
    <string name="parvati_nick">MADE FOR THE HEXADOME</string>
    <string name="parvati_moto">TACTICAL ANALYSIS COMPLETE. CONFIDENCE OF VICTORY AT 97.83\%.</string>
    <string name="parvati_abstract">She\'s indefatigably, maximally devoted to her team. If there is a limit to her capacity for self-improvement, we have yet to see a sign of it. She will heal, repair, assess, fight, and even score if necessary. Parvati performs all her roles so dependably that she\'s been a staple of the Interplanetary Aristeia! Team Managers Association\'s All-Star team for twenty years straight, and still going strong.\n</string>
    <string name="parvati_description">Parvati is a permanent memento for the early days of Aristeia!, when only synthetic bodies were allowed to fight.\n
        It’s been twenty-five years since the first Aristeia! cast. Back then, it was called Yajurveda, and was conceived as gladiatorial combat between Aspects of ALEPH—among them, our beloved Parvati—wearing otherworldly synth bods. The show had been running for four years when its first ever human contender rose to the top. The audience fell in love with her fierceness and physicality, so much so that the channel was emboldened to pivot towards meat-on-meat fighting and slowly phase the machines out.\n
        Today, only Parvati remains as a vestige of those first runs, her claim to fame unchallenged. Parvati’s learning module was programmed by ALEPH with a focus on teamwork and field medicine, and with successive iterations she has become a veritable staple of the game. Naturally, Parvati is supremely effective at patching her teammates up in a rush, but what garnered her a spot among the all-time Bahadurs is her ability to do that while still scoring and taking out the competition. She’s known to be a second wind that can carry even the most disastrous game to victory.\n
        Each year, Parvati has regaled us with a specially-designed casing to suit that season’s overarching theme. Last season’s HexaDomes recreated the untamed mountains of Ariadna and Parvati flaunted the look of a rugged frontierswoman. This time she’s chosen retro stylings to take us back to her debut, updating that classic design but reminding her fans that deep down she’s a highly sophisticated android.\n
        After so many years in the spotlight, Parvati is a bona fide international celebrity, recognized for her work both inside the HexaDome and outside. With her learning module always collating and processing every game and every fight, only one question remains:\n
        Is there a ceiling to Parvati’s evolution?\</string>

    <string name="lunah_name">MAJOR LUNAH</string>
    <string name="lunah_nick">DISCIPLINED AND LETHAL</string>
    <string name="lunah_moto">YOU CAN RUN, BUT YOU CAN\'T HIDE.</string>
    <string name="lunah_abstract">As deliberate and lethal as the venomous snakes of her home planet, Major Lunah surrenders the spotlight only up until the moment she decides to make the kill. Her military rank is more than a marketing scheme; she has served her nation in some of the deadliest theatres of operation in the Human Sphere. Now, she\´s come to bring some much-needed discipline to the world of show biz.\n</string>
    <string name="lunah_description">This decorated markswoman—she holds the rank of Rā\'id in the Haqqislamite armed forces —entered the pro Aristeia! circuit only two years ago, and she’s already caused quite a splash.\n
        The forty-three-year-old war hero boasts an impressive service record, including not one, not two, but three tours as an elite sharpshooter on Paradiso, where she helped keep the alien invaders of the Combined Army at bay, lest they gain a foothold in their encroachment of the Human Sphere.\n
        For reasons she refuses to disclose, two years ago Major Lunah resigned her military commission and became an Aristeia! aspirant. She had the approval and support of her superiors at the Haqqislamite army and, as it turned out, of the Haqqislamite people at large—audience ratings in Haqqislam have skyrocketed since her debut.\n
        Major Lunah has introduced bona fide military discipline into the world of Aristeia! And, in a sport where warfare is so ostentatiously invoked, it seems the audience has gotten a taste for the real thing. Luckily for them, Major Lunah has a competitive streak, as evidenced by her celebration of every new notch on her gun. She has proven that a sniper can play as crucial a role in a team as any other combatant. Despite her stern rictus and martial demeanor, there’s cheers every time she comes out of nowhere and turns the tide of a game with a surgical max-range shot. And each time she pulls off one of her trademark ricochets, her merchandise flies off the shelf for weeks.\n
        Accurate, serene, courteous in her dealings with journalists and fans, she’s a real pro. Major Lunah has promised us a finale twist that sports aficionados won’t soon forget.\n
        Could the hour of revelation be nigh?\</string>

    <string name="hexx3r_name">HEXX3R</string>
    <string name="hexx3r_nick"> THE NOMAD WITCH</string>
    <string name="hexx3r_moto">EXITUS ACTA PROBAT</string>
    <string name="hexx3r_abstract">The \'Nomad Witch\' has worked hard for that moniker. Whenever she\'s in the arena, everyone else is at risk of becoming an unwitting pawn or a mindless puppet. With a pull of her string, a foe flies off the scoring zone like a broken doll; with a curt order, a friend advances an agenda only hEXx3r truly understands.\n</string>
    <string name="hexx3r_description">The enigmatic Nomad hacker known only as hEXx3r is responsible for a revolution in the role played by software in Aristeia!\n
        More than any other hacker in the brief stretch that the discipline has been applied to Aristeia! hEXx3r has changed the face of the game forever. In record time, she has proven capable of turning the tide of a match by sending her opponents into disarray at the worst possible moment. Armed with nothing but software, hEXx3r gives the heavyweights a run for their money. She freezes them, exposes them and then throws them into ambuscades choreographed at the speed of thought. The words “that Nomad witch” are often muttered by players as they’re carted out of the HexaDome.\n
        Her fans blame her strained reputation on ‘smear campaigns’ by PanOceanian media, but the truth is she has slipped comfortably into the role of a termagant and used it to boost her mystique. So far, it’s served her well. Her brand recognition numbers are outstanding and she’s a well-loved figure among non-conformists and antiestablishmentarians even beyond the borders of the Nomad Nation.\n
        hEXx3r hails from the Nomad mothership Tunguska, and her… unusual hacking device reflects that. Although its inner workings are a closely guarded secret, experts believe hEXx3r’s mask is part of a neural interface and that her gloves play a key role in giving her software access to the HexaDome fixtures, but beyond that it’s all conjecture.\n
        In the absence of official data, theories abound: from esoteric alien technology to the idea that hEXx3r herself was grown in a vat in some Praxis lab researching human telekinetic capabilities. But if you ask the average fan, they’ll have a simpler explanation:\n
        It’s legit witchcraft!\”</string>

    <string name="ball_name">8-BALL</string>
    <string name="ball_nick">THE CHARMING BLACK SHEEP</string>
    <string name="ball_moto">YOU KNOW ME; I SEE AN OPENING, I GOTTA PLAY BALL.</string>
    <string name="ball_abstract">Showmanship made (panda) flesh, a poet in the medium of randomness, \'Baller\' crashes the HexaDome like he crashes a party: unavoidably and unpredictably. He rolls like a powerful opening break, only this ball is calling all the shots. 8-Ball is the pain in any team manager\'s ass and the life of every party worthy of that name.\n</string>
    <string name="ball_description">He’s the eighth heir to a caste of Aristeia! champions, a beloved media superstar and an outrageous sex-symbol, but he’s always fallen just a little short of snatching the coveted title of Bahadur.\n
        8-Ball hails from Bakunin, the weirdest of the three motherships of the Nomad Nation. If the Bakunin society has one salient trait, it’s a tolerance for all things different and eccentric. A specific borough inside Bakunin, called VaudeVille, is the Human Sphere’s most fertile soil for artistic endeavor, sordid indulgence and extravagant lavishness. One discipline lies at the intersection of all three: body modification. For the right money, you can get panther eyes, live wire hair… or panda fur.\n
        No dark arts are responsible for 8-Ball’s prodigious size and strength; he was always going to be buff and deceptively agile for his massive size. Cheeky, impudent and carefree, at least he has the skills to back up all his bravado. As for his family, from a very early age they enabled his addiction to extreme sports in lieu of training for his rightful destiny: the crown of Aristeia! Bahadur.\n
        Will this be the season 8-Ball finally realizes his legacy?\n</string>

    <string name="mushashi_name">MIYAMOTO MUSHASHI</string>
    <string name="mushashi_nick">THE EDGE UNREMITTING</string>
    <string name="mushashi_moto">KNOW YOUR ENEMY; KNOW THEIR BLADE.</string>
    <string name="mushashi_abstract">If you were to synthesize pure combat prowess, the formula would have to contain the mind of the most renowned fighter in history, plus the most advanced artificial body ever designed. Luckily for us, Aristeia! has already gone to the trouble of manufacturing this volatile concoction, and all that\'s left for us is to kick back and enjoy the spectacle that is Miyamoto Mushashi.\n</string>
    <string name="mushashi_description">Miyamoto Mushashi is a faithfully rendered biosynthetic Recreation of the emblematic 16th-century Japanese master swordsman.\n
        ‘Project Duelist’ was carried out at the request of the VissioRama media channel for their Aristeia! venture. After a fig-leaf renaming for legal reasons, VissioRama deployed an ambitious branding scheme to make a channel-wide star out of their very own Recreation. They requested an updated version of the historical personality so he could star in a modern-day musha-shugyo, the warrior’s pilgrimage undergone by Miyamoto between 1605 and 1612. The show has followed the Recreation’s exploits across the Human Sphere, including his duels against other Aristos he’s encountered in his travels.\n
        The first few seasons have been nothing short of a smash hit. Mushashi has ridden a wave of critical acclaim, audience retention and fan engagement all the way to the top of the rankings and the title of Bahadur faster than any fighter before him, but his future is uncertain. His austere, composed personality is ill-suited to the frivolity of Aristeia! stardom and his efficient, no-frills dueling style makes for unsatisfactory fighting sequences. Increasingly, commentators are starting to wonder: What does VissioRama have in store for Miyamoto Mushashi?\n</string>

    <string name="wildbill_name">WILD BILL</string>
    <string name="wildbill_nick">THE MYSTERIOUS GUNSLINGER</string>
    <string name="wildbill_moto">I\'VE DANCED WITH THE REAPER MORE\'N A FEW TIMES MYSELF. NOW SHE DANCES TO MY TUNE.</string>
    <string name="wildbill_abstract">If Wild Bill is in the mix, you know there\'s a wager going on. The higher the risk, the sweeter his inevitable reward. A bona fide card shark and unerring gunslinger, this mysterious, anachronistic gentleman fixated on the march of time is this season\'s leading contender to the title of Bahadur. If you want to win big, go ahead and bet against him, but be aware: so far he hasn\'t lost a gamble.\n</string>
    <string name="wildbill_description">Wild Bill is so committed to his historical namesake he’s spun a legend out of the barrels of his twin revolvers.\n
        James Butler Hickok introduced himself to the showrunners during a live broadcast on Dawn, the planet of the Ariadnan nation. For his first public appearance, he was already in-character as Wild Bill: he showed up on horseback, armed with two guns with mother of pearl grips, and wearing a wide-brimmed hat, a duster coat, and hide boots with spurs.\n
        As it turns out, he already had an exceptional résumé as an adventurer. He had been one of the few survivors of the Day of the Dead Man, which he finished carrying only a hunting rifle, a handful of bullets, a canteen of water and an antique pocketwatch. A remarkable feat to pull off.\n
        Everything about Wild Bill is from a bygone era, down to the way he walks, his anachronistic turns of phrase and his pocketwatch—a genuine piece of 19th-century Americana he unfailingly checks each time he guns down an opponent in the arena.\n
        Despite his old-fashioned persona, Wild Bill has a very modern eye for the parameters of a spectacle capable of making the audience tick. The thunder of his guns is the soundtrack to a tale of derring-do full of grisly plot twists.\n
        After five seasons of buildup, everyone agrees that the cowboy is perfectly poised to take a shot at Miyamoto for the league crown.\n
        His time is fast approaching, maybe that’s why his eyes are glued to his watch?\n</string>

    <string name="gata_name">GATA</string>
    <string name="gata_nick">THERE\'S NO SPEED LIMIT ON THE WAY TO THE TOP!</string>
    <string name="gata_moto">THERE\'S NO SPEED LIMIT ON THE WAY TO THE TOP!</string>
    <string name="gata_abstract">The newest addition to the star-studded halls of Aristeia! is so fast she seems to be everywhere at once, and every camera lens works double to keep up with her, both inside and outside the HexaDome. Gata\'s upbeat, vibrant personality makes her merchandise fly off the shelves as quickly as she flies over her opponent\'s heads.\n</string>
    <string name="gata_description">The latest teenage idol to grace our screens is a little orphan who made a dizzying journey from destitution to superstardom.\n
        Cátia was born in the Belagua favela on planet Acontecimento, where hunger pushed her to a childhood of larceny. Her self-preservation instincts taught her to pick a pocket or lift a piece of fruit, and then make a dash for it. Run for it, and keep running. She grew up fleeing every danger, but danger was always half a step behind. Even as she dodged the prostitution rings that swallow so many lives like hers, she found herself taking courier jobs for the kind of people one can’t afford to disappoint. That kept her head above water for a few days, but money never lasted long.\n
        At sixteen, her luck finally turned. Desperate to leave Acontecimento, she stole a briefcase from a businesswoman who was clearly guarding something valuable. She thought fencing it would pay for her ticket into space and a clean start somewhere else, but the woman’s bodyguards had other plans. These weren’t the apathetic cops she was used to, they were well-trained mercenaries who tracked her like hounds.\n
        In the free-running chase that ensued, Cátia unknowingly broke into the set of a film being shot. Even though the security agents were in peak physical shape, the girl humiliated them with her acrobatics on her way to the exit. Among the many witnesses was a renowned talent scout named Sophia Kreuziger, who requested a copy of the footage so she could examine the young thief’s pirouettes.\n
        Cátia was ultimately captured, but Sophia and her lawyers interceded and managed to convince the owner of the briefcase to drop all charges. In return for Sophia’s legal and professional representation, Cátia fulfilled her dream to move off-planet, and Sophia got a new star—one which would shine brightly indeed—at a steal.\n
        Will Gata outrun her competitors to the top of the charts?\n</string>

    <string name="hannibal_name">HANNIBAL</string>
    <string name="hannibal_nick">MERC TEAM LEADER</string>
    <string name="hannibal_moto">I LOVE IT WHEN A PLAN COMES TOGETHER.</string>
    <string name="hannibal_abstract">Hannibal is both manager and fighter of his own team. A natural born leader inside and outside the HexaDome. He doesn’t stand out because of his combat skills, but because of his ability to help his teammates get a jump on the enemy. He is a total strategist, intelligent, capable of reading and understanding the game to his benefit. A skill developed in a world where there are no second chances.\n</string>
    <string name="hannibal_description">Hannibal is the Man with the Plan, the foremost strategic mind in Aristeia! and a natural born leader inside the HexaDome and out.\n
        This dapper man styles himself a businessman rather than a brawler, which isn’t far from the truth. The only caveat resides in his particular areas of expertise, namely warfare, private security and his latest venture: combat-as-spectacle.\n
        The truth about Hannibal’s past is hard to pin down. If you take him at his word, he came from money, but the collapse of his family fortune forced him to drop out of university and accept a position at an intelligence agency. It was the eve of the NeoColonial Wars, and Hannibal claims to have received decorations from several allied governments during the conflict. After the war, Hannibal—more interested in maintaining his upscale lifestyle than in military accolades—promptly branched off into the private sector. As a military contractor he was well-poised to exploit a growing demand for private security and the confidential exchange of any number of products, including sensitive information and extra-legal merchandise. Naturally, no evidence exists to connect him with any illicit activities, so either he’s embellishing the truth or he did a good job of covering his tracks.\n
        On the back of his business acumen, Hannibal has lived expansively in every capital in the Human Sphere, indulged every pleasure and even amassed quite the art collection. His greatest accomplishment was his position at Van Orton’s Foreign Company, perhaps the most high-profile mercenary outfit in the Sphere, famous for providing security for a number of showbiz celebrities. As Van Orton’s second-in-command and Chief Strategy Officer, Hannibal was able to cultivate the associations he needed to dip his toe in the Aristeia! pool. Turns out his discerning eye and military experience were perfectly suited to the sport, and soon enough Hannibal was bankrolling his own team, a team of hard-boiled mercenaries in his own image.\n
        Speaking of hard-boiled, the undisputed star of the team is Señor Massacre, a man with a long history of driving his fellow soldiers of fortune crazy with his tireless chatter and boundless ego. Another of Hannibal’s picks is a mercurial woman called Laxmee, a self-taught hacker boasting the mercenary pedigree of her native Corregidor. Rounding up the team is the awe-inspiring Valkyrie, a formidable sellsword and loyal bodyguard to Hannibal. The team is a well-oiled fighting machine led by a dubious moral compass.\n
        The same dubious morality informs Hannibal’s dealings outside the HexaDome. Despite his success as an Aristo and team owner, Hannibal has maintained a working relationship with Van Orton and his Foreign Company. Since Hannibal isn’t adverse to actual field work, Van Orton has been offering him noteworthy jobs to raise his team’s public profile or, alternatively, covert operations with iron-clad confidentiality clauses and extortionate rates.\n
        Inside the HexaDome, Hannibal plays the role of a leader and tactician. He studies his foes before, during and after each game, always looking for a weakness to exploit and assessing the right moment to strike for maximum impact. He’s far from the toughest fighter in the circuit, but his intelligence and cunning set him apart from the chaff. With him at the helm, his team always has the wit to seize the upper hand and the guts to bash the other team to death with it.\n
        “Hell, yeah. I love it when a plan comes together.”\n</string>

    <string name="valkyrie_name">VALKYRIE</string>
    <string name="valkyrie_nick">THE NORSE FURY</string>
    <string name="valkyrie_moto">¡VICTORIA O VALHALA!</string>
    <string name="valkyrie_abstract">Blunt as a sledgehammer. Valkyrie charges to the Scoring Zone and seizes it. If Valkyrie has chosen you, there’s no place in the HexaDome where you can hide. She will find you, and she will beat you. Or worse, she will trap you and make you watch your team’s defeat.\n</string>
    <string name="valkyrie_description">After leaving behind a life of thievery and pillage aboard a pirate vessel, Valkyrie has finally found her true calling inside the HexaDome. Whoever stands between her and the title of Bahadur she will gladly crush underfoot.\n
        From her nom de guerre to her appearance—bulging muscles, long blond braids—to her weapon of choice, everything about Valkyrie suggests a shard of Norse mythology come to life under the thick permafrost of the planet Svalarheima. And she might very well be exactly that, given the gaps in our knowledge of her past, the truth of which lies buried under permafrost-thick layers of ‘access denied’ sigils.\n
        This is what we do know: as a teenager, Mia Anderson obtained a brief measure of infamy as a crew member of the Defiler. Whatever she did before joining one of the most reviled pirate crews in recent memory, nobody knows—or rather no one’s telling. Despite her youth, Anderson’s imposing physique made her a key player in the Defiler’s boarding team. Her role boiled down to clearing a path through corridors and cargo bays, crushing any opposition in the way. Apparently, Anderson took to charging straight at enemy barricades armed with little more than a heavy axe and a war cry, and even the most steadfast defense fell like a house of cards before her warrior’s advance.\n
        But, as they say, a pirate can either be famous or long-lived. The Defiler’s reputation for savagery and audacity eventually drew the attention of the Mayasphere. After making one too many headlines, the ship’s fate was sealed when the Foreign Company—the Human Sphere’s most media-friendly mercenary company—took on a bounty against it. The bounty had been co-financed by the Maya channel Oxyd, who owned the media rights to whatever story unfolded from the chase.\n
        Hannibal—the strategic mastermind behind many of the Foreign Company’s successes—put together one of his visionary plans and lured the Defiler into the trap that would end its larcenous career. Once the trap was sprung, the mercenaries boarded the Defiler and, inch by hard-fought inch, wrestled control of the ship from its crew under the supervision of Hannibal and the gaze of Oxyd’s drone cameras. This was the world’s first chance to see Mia Anderson in action, fighting to repel an attack as vicious as the ones her crew had wrought. She was eventually captured, but not before she downed four of the Hannibal’s men.\n
        The authorities looked leniently upon Mia’s case, and she was sent to a juvenile correctional facility. A few years later, when she was released from the system, a certain businessman named Hannibal was waiting for her with an offer: a position on his budding Aristeia! team, which he planned to staff with the societal refuse of the Human Sphere.\n
        Since that day Valkyrie has proved herself against the likes of Maximus and Miyamoto Mushashi, and has become a front-runner for the title of Bahadur. Nobody seems likely to stop her now, for who could staunch the flow of an avalanche?\n</string>

    <string name="laxmee_name">LAXMEE</string>
    <string name="laxmee_nick">THE UNPREDICTABLE MAASAI HACKER</string>
    <string name="laxmee_moto">MAYA HAS ITS OWN SPIRITS, AND I AM THEIR LAIBON.</string>
    <string name="laxmee_abstract">People come in two flavors: those who use Maya, and those who understand it. Laxmee doesn’t just read Maya, she converses with it. She has that intuition. She can influence her teammates, or her enemies, with subtleness and discretion. Her programs are those little weights that end up tipping the balance in her favor.\n</string>
    <string name="laxmee_description">The infohacker Laxmee conjures up programs like a Maasai laibon calls down the rains.\n
        The Maasai were a tribe of proud warriors and hunters, but they were driven out of their native Africa and resettled aboard the Nomad mothership Corregidor. As a young girl of Maasai descent, Laxmee seemed doomed to feed the cycle of criminality plaguing Corregidorian youth, especially once she enrolled in one of the gangs vying for control over the more impoverished fringe sectors of the ship. One momentous day, her gang hit a supply barge moored on their turf and found a shipping container full of military equipment. When it came time to divvy up the swag, Laxmee ignored firearms and ammunition as soon as a particular piece of gear caught her eye: an honest-to-goodness infowar hacking device. But, by gang rules, everyone who wanted that piece would have to fight for it. Laxmee never backed down—she was too true to her Maasai heritage for that—and one by one the other contenders bit the dust, earning her the prize.\n
        But the gang leaders didn’t realize the army would never forfeit that kind of materiel, and within hours they were in the custody of the military police. Laxmee had no illusions about her bosses’ ability to withstand a Corregidor-style ‘debriefing’, so she resolved to abscond with her toy rather than wait for the other shoe to drop. She stowed away on a random freighter and thus begun her journey across space stations and caravanserai the Sphere over, always carrying her hacking device, always a fugitive of the law.\n
        Laxmee took to programming very soon, and her abilities grew as she met other underground hackers on her travels and constructed a network of contacts. Maya, the interplanetary data network, became her only true home. Soon, breaking encryptions and stealing secured data became routine. Using counterfeit qualifications, she was able to quit dock work and get herself a cozier job as IT at a recreational cruiser, which left her plenty of free time to moonlight as an information broker. Her new job also gained her access to multitude of high-value targets such as megacorp executives and travelers with suspiciously high-security comlogs. After getting the data, Laxmee only had to sit on it for a prudent amount of time before hawking it in the black market. It was a solid, profitable system, but the sensation of impunity was too heady for Laxmee, and she became overambitious.\n
        One night in particular, she broke into a portable data vault owned by an eccentric-looking businessman. It was a clean job, quick and traceless, but then again all her jobs were clean. Only when she opened the decoy data did she realize her mistake, but before she could react the door came crashing down. A gigantic blonde marched into her cabin and pinned her against the bulkhead. The bogus businessman sauntered in after his associate, smiling appreciatively.\n
        “Outstanding job, kid. My name’s Hannibal, as you might have deduced,” he said, nodding toward the screen. “I’ve been looking for someone with your kind of talent. I’m gonna make you an offer you can’t refuse.”\n
        “Maya has its own spirits, and I am their laibon.”\n</string>

    <string name="massacre_name">SEÑOR MASACRE</string>
    <string name="massacre_nick"> THE BLOOD SPECTACLE</string>
    <string name="massacre_moto">WITH PALS LIKE ME, WHO NEEDS ENEMAS?</string>
    <string name="massacre_abstract">Merc and showman, Señor Massacre is as violent as he is chatty. His military past provides him with enough experience to honor his stage name. In the middle of the fight, katanas in his hands, the result tends to be a lot of mortally wounded enemies, to say the least. His constant mockery of the show, everyone else, and himself, is just his way of constantly avoiding a past that haunts him, trying to drive him crazy.\n</string>
    <string name="massacre_description">Mercenary and showman, Señor Massacre is as violent as he is chatty.\n
        In his heyday, Señor Massacre led a brilliant career in the underground fighting ring of Corregidor. He was legitimately good, an agile, intuitive fighter and, for a long while, a safe bet in the ring. But fame went to his head and drugs quickly followed, and Señor Massacre lost his edge and, with it, one too many bets. To shake his debtors, he dropped the luchador persona and enlisted in the Nomad Military Force. He volunteered for a forward outpost, where he learned proper teamwork and regained his combat senses. During the NeoColonial Wars he was the only commando to survive the boarding of the Sun Jiao battle cruiser and the subsequent shipwreck. He lived, but not unscathed: radiation burns, and military-grade assault viruses disfigured him beyond the help of even the most experimental regenerative treatments Bakunin could offer.\n
        Once discharged from the NMF, Señor Massacre became a freelance military contractor under his old pseudonym. Records show that he led a corsair boarding crew off Human Edge, worked for the Puños Rojos guerrilla on the jungles of Central America, acted as saboteur for the ecoterrorist group Eco-Aktion, and had a brief stint as a bodyguard for a Tien Shan drug lord. For a while he even went back to the fighting rings, but this time on the major leagues: Aristeia! Underground, where his bravado and showmanship earned him as much praise as his spec-ops brand of hard-boiled viciousness.\n
        His team has performed so well this season that this year will be one of the best of Aristeia! His nerve and shamelessness in front of the cameras have earned him a lot of fans throughout the Human Sphere.\n
        “You people don’t appreciate me at all! To you I’m just this ‘cool mercenary’ guy with a cute little butt and two sweet-ass katanas. Well, I can cook too, you know!”\n</string>

</resources>
